hey folks so let's talk now about
大家好，让我们现在谈谈
optimal auctions and what we mean by
最佳拍卖以及我们的意思
optimal auctions basically and up until
最佳拍卖基本上直到
this point in the course usually when
在课程中的这一点通常是
we've been analyzing auctions we've
我们一直在分析拍卖
taken auctions as given and analyzed
按既定进行拍卖并进行分析
them or we've talked a little bit about
他们，或者我们谈论了一些
optimal efficient auctions in terms of
在以下方面进行最佳有效拍卖
victory claros mechanisms and so forth
胜利宣言机制等
and here the idea is that we'll think
这里的想法是我们会认为
about a seller designing an auction and
关于设计拍卖的卖方，以及
the seller might have incentives not
卖方可能没有激励
necessarily to always do the efficient
必须始终做到高效
thing but instead to maximize the price
东西，而是最大化价格
that they get the expected price so
他们得到了预期的价格，所以
they're interested in maximizing
他们有兴趣最大化
expected revenue and what does that mean
预期收入，这意味着什么
in terms of possible losses and
就可能的损失而言
efficiency it may mean that that
效率可能意味着
sometimes the seller doesn't sell the
有时卖方不出售
good so they may risk failing to sell it
好，这样他们可能会冒无法出售的风险
they might also even sell to a buyer
他们甚至可能卖给买家
that doesn't necessarily have the
不一定有
highest bid and that could happen in
最高出价，这可能会在
settings where there's some asymmetries
不对称的设置
among buyers and you want to use one
买家之间，您想使用一个
buyer the threat of selling to one buyer
买家威胁要卖给一位买家
to make sure that you increase the bids
确保您提高出价
by the other buyer and we'll see a
由其他买家提供，我们将看到一个
little bit of that in a bit so here
一点点，所以这里
we're going to think now about optimal
我们现在要考虑最佳
auctions in this narrow sense of trying
在这种狭sense的尝试中进行拍卖
to design an auction which is going to
设计一个拍卖会
maximize the sellers revenue so what
最大化卖方收入
what kind of setting are we going to
我们要去什么样的环境
look at will keep things relatively
看会保持相对
simple in terms of the structure so one
就结构而言很简单
good to be sold
好卖
private valuation so each buyer has some
私人估价，因此每个买家都有一些
value for the good they're each risk
物有所值，每个风险
neutral the bidders valuation is going
中立投标人的估价
to be drawn from a nice distribution
从良好的分布中得出
that CDF is a cumulative distribution
CDF是累积分布
function so we have a cumulative
功能，所以我们有一个累积
distribution function f I with a PDF
PDF的分布函数f I
density function of F I which is going
FI的密度函数
to be continuous and bounded below so
是连续的并在下面限制
nicely define continuous distributions
很好地定义连续分布
over value so a uniform distribution or
值过高，因此分布均匀或
a series of other distributions that
一系列其他分布
will keep things nicely shaped we're
会保持形状良好，我们
going to allow for asymmetries
将允许不对称
among the individual so now we're going
在个人之间，所以现在我们要
to allow one bidder to have one
让一个投标人有一个
distribution and another bidder to have
分配和另一个投标人
a different distribution so it could be
不同的分布，所以它可能是
that I think of some bidders as having
我认为有些投标人有
deep pockets and high values and other
财大气粗，物超所值
bidders as as being more thrifty and not
投标人认为更节俭而不是
having as high a value for an object so
具有很高的价值
we're going to have different
我们将有不同
distributions and the important thing is
分布，重要的是
that the risk-neutral seller here is
这里的风险中立卖方是
going to know the distributions and has
会知道分布并有
no value for the object so zero value
该对象无值，因此零值
for the object knows the distributions
因为对象知道分布
but doesn't know the actual values so it
但不知道实际值，所以
has an idea of of what range the the
对什么范围
values are and what the relative
值是和相对的
probabilities of different values are
不同值的概率是
but does not know the precise values
但不知道精确值
okay so the optimal auction here we're
好的，所以我们在这里进行最佳拍卖
going to be looking at an auction that
要去看拍卖
maximizes the sellers expected revenue
最大化卖方预期收入
subject to some form of individual
服从某种形式的个人
rationality in this particular case is
在这种情况下的合理性是
not going to matter so much which type
哪种类型无关紧要
of individual rationality we impose we
我们强加于个人理性
can think of it as ex-post or interim
可以将其视为事后或临时
you can always move things around in
你总是可以在里面移动东西
terms of expected payments given all the
鉴于所有
risk neutrality and the transferability
风险中性和可转移性
here so we want Bayesian a set of
在这里，我们想要贝叶斯一套
compatibility and make sure that the
兼容性，并确保
buyers don't want to walk away from the
买家不想离开
auction okay we're going to think about
拍卖行，我们要考虑一下
optimal auctions okay
最佳拍卖行
so what I'm gonna do is start with a
所以我要做的是从
simple example and based on an example
一个简单的例子，并基于一个例子
we'll get some intuitions out for why
我们会得到一些直觉，为什么
things are working and then we'll do a
一切正常，然后我们将
general statement of a theorem and so
定理的一般性陈述等
here well let's start with two bidders
好吧，让我们从两个竞标者开始
each has a value uniformly distributed
每个都有一个均匀分布的值
on 0 1 and let's think of changing the
在0 1上，让我们考虑更改
auction in a very simple format what
以非常简单的格式拍卖
we're gonna do is stick in a reserve
我们要做的就是保留储备金
price okay and this is quite common in
价格还可以，这在
auction so often when people are selling
人们出售时经常拍卖
things off there'll be a minimum bid a
事情将有一个最低出价
reserve price and you're not allowed to
底价，你不能
enter into the bidding unless you exceed
参加竞标，除非您超过
that threshold and so we're going to set
该阈值，所以我们要设置
a reverse reserve price and here we're
反向底价，我们在这里
gonna have a second price auction to
将要进行第二次价格拍卖
make life simple keep with the dominant
使生活简单，保持优势
strategies but just stick in a reserve
策略，但只是保留
price okay so let's think about how this
价格还可以，所以让我们考虑一下
works
作品
once we've put in a reserve price then
一旦我们设定了底价
if both people end up bidding below that
如果两个人最终都低于该价格
we're not gonna get anything so we and
我们不会得到任何东西，所以我们和
here's the risk now if we didn't have a
如果我们没有一个
reserve price we would always sell the
底价我们将永远卖出
object now there's a possibility of no
对象，现在有没有可能性
sale so we're not going to get anything
销售，所以我们不会得到任何东西
if one bidder bids above the reserve and
如果一个投标人的出价超出了储备金，并且
one below it then the reserve price is
一个低于它的底价是
going to kick in that's going to be the
要踢的将是
second highest price the second highest
第二高的价格第二高的价格
bid we'll think of the reserve price as
出价，我们将底价视为
if it was a bid and the second highest
如果是出价并且是第二高的
bid is now the reserve price and so
现在的出价是底价，因此
we'll sell at that reserve if somebody
如果有人，我们将以该储备金出售
bids above it and the other below so
出价高于它，另一个低于
again second price auction that's going
再次进行第二次价格拍卖
to be the second highest and if both of
是第二高的，如果两者
them been above it if both bidders
如果两个竞标者都在上面
happen a bit above it then it'll just be
发生在它上面一点，那将是
the second highest bid that will be the
第二高的出价将是
price okay so that's the setting and
价格还可以，所以这是设置
which reserve price is going to maximize
哪个底价将最大化
the expected revenue so let's take a
预期收入，所以让我们
look at that so first thing to note it's
看着那个，首先要注意的是
still a dominant strategy to bid your
仍然是竞标您的主要策略
true value and in fact you could think
真正的价值，实际上你会想到
of the reserve price is just like a
底价的
third bidder in this case and so from
在这种情况下，第三竞标者
any bidders perspective you still want
您仍然想要的任何竞标者观点
to be bidding your true value if it's a
竞标您的真实价值，如果它是
second price auction where you think of
您想到的第二次价格拍卖
this reserve prices if it's just a fixed
如果只是固定价格
bid out there you just happen to know
竞标在那里，你只是知道
what one of the bids are it's still a
到底是哪一个出价
dominant strategy to bid your true value
发挥您的真实价值的主导策略
so that makes our life easy in terms of
这样就使我们的生活更轻松
the analysis so if both sale if both
分析，如果两者都出售
bids are below our that's going to
出价低于我们的出价
happen now with probability R squared
现在发生，概率R平方
because people are bidding truthfully so
因为人们真实地竞标
the chance that they're both below R
他们都低于R的机会
with a uniform distribution independent
具有独立的均匀分布
draws of uniform distribution
均匀分布图
probability that any one of them is
其中任何一个是
below is our so the probability that
下面是我们的概率
both of them are below is R squared in
它们都在下面R平方中
that case the revenue 0 the chance that
这种情况下，收益为0的机会
one's above and one below well the
一个人在上面，一个人在下面
chance of one's above is 1 minus R the
一个人以上的机会是1减去R
other ones below is R and it can happen
下面的其他是R，并且可能发生
in two different ways in terms of which
以两种不同的方式
bidder is above and which bidders below
投标者在上方，投标人在下方
in that case the second highest price is
在这种情况下，第二高的价格是
the reserve price that's the revenue and
底价即收益，
then
然后
in a case where they're both above
如果它们都在上面
that's going to happen with probability
这将有可能发生
one minus R squared and in that case
1减去R的平方
then we're going to get the expected
然后我们将获得预期的
minimum of the two values conditional on
两个条件中的最小值
both of the values being above R and if
两个值都高于R，并且如果
you just work out the integral of what's
你只要算出什么是不可或缺的
the expected minimum of two uniformly
预期的最小值2
distributed random variables conditional
分布随机变量条件
on those variables going between our two
关于我们两个之间的变量
one right so now they fall both within
一种权利，所以现在它们都属于
our two one figure out what the expected
我们两个弄清楚了期望
minimum of that is I'll save you the
最少的是我会救你
algebra it's 1 plus 2 R over 2 over 3 ok
代数是1加2 R超过2超过3可以
so when we look at these then we do the
因此，当我们查看这些内容时，我们会
overall expected revenue what do we get
总体预期收入我们能得到什么
we've got this probability that we're
我们有这种可能性
going to get a revenue of R so multiply
要获得R的收入，所以相乘
those out we get to R squared 1 minus R
那些我们得到R平方1减去R
here and then we've got this probability
在这里，然后我们有这个可能性
of that both people are above and then
这两个人都在之上，然后
we have this expected revenue so we end
我们有这个预期的收入，所以我们结束
up with an overall expected revenue of
总预期收入为
this expression because if they're both
这个表达是因为如果他们俩
below we don't get anything so that's
下面我们什么都没得到，那是
the overall expression that's the
整体表达是
expected revenue if we collect terms
如果我们收集条款，预计收入
here in terms of ours you can simplify
就我们而言，您可以简化
this so the expected revenue here is
因此，这里的预期收入是
given by this expression 1 plus 3 R
由该表达式给出1加3 R
squared minus 4 hours cubed over 3 so
减去3的平方减去4小时
now we have an expression for revenue
现在我们有一个收入表达
just maximize that with respect to R so
只是相对于R最大化
let's take the derivative with respect
让我们尊重派生
to R and set that equal to 0
到R并将其设置为等于0
what do you get 0 equals 2 R minus 4 R
您得到的0等于2 R减去4 R
squared solving that R is equal to 1/2
R等于1/2的平方解
so what does that tell us if you're
那么这告诉我们您是否
facing two bidders in a second-price
面对两个竞标者的第二价格
auction uniform values between 0 & 1
拍卖统一价值（介于0和1之间）
you set a reserve price of 1/2 that's
您将底价定为1/2，即
going to maximize the expected revenue
将使预期收益最大化
okay
好的
you can do calculations so suppose let's
您可以进行计算，所以假设
do our calculation when we set the
当我们设置
reserve price of 1/2 what do we earn in
底价的1/2我们能赚到什么
terms of revenue well you can stick your
收入方面，你可以坚持你的
1/2 in here do the calculation you end
1/2在这里做你结束的计算
up with 5 twelfths
十二分之五
if you set a reserve price of zero then
如果您将底价设置为零，则
the expected revenue you get zeros for
预期收益为零
the R's you get one-third here so you
R是你的三分之一，所以你
end up with a lower this is just for 12
最终以较低的价格仅售12
right so we end up with a higher
对，所以我们最终得到了更高的
expected revenue when we set the reserve
设定准备金时的预期收入
price at 1/2 so increasing that reserve
价格为1/2，因此增加了储备金
price increases the expected revenue for
价格提高了预期的收入
the seller now you don't want to you
卖方现在你不想你
know the the 1/2 was nicely chosen if we
知道1/2是很好的选择，如果我们
set it too high then you have no chance
设置得太高，那么你就没有机会
that you're going to end up with a sale
你最终将要出售
and then your profits actually go down
然后您的利润实际上下降了
so it's hitting a sweet spot in terms of
所以它在以下方面达到了最佳效果
what the reserve price was so the
底价是多少
trade-offs here you lose sales when both
权衡取舍时，您都失去了销售
bids were below 1/2 by setting this
将此设置为低于1/2的出价
reserve price but that was a low revenue
底价，但这是低收入
in any case and it only has a
无论如何，它只有一个
probability of 1/4 of happening you
发生你的1/4的概率
increase the the price when one of the
增加价格时，其中之一
bidder was low and the other one was
竞标者很低，另一个是
high and it actually happens with the
高，实际上发生在
probability of 1/2 and so in this case
在这种情况下为1/2的概率
increasing that reserve price led to
增加底价导致
higher revenue because the increase you
更高的收入，因为增加了您
got from here more than offset the
从这里得到的不只是抵消了
decrease you got by losing sales when
通过减少销售而减少
both bids happen to be low ok so you can
两种出价都较低，可以
think of adding this reserve prices as
考虑将这个底价添加为
if you're adding a third bidder it's
如果您要添加第三位竞标者，
sort of increasing the competition in
在某种程度上增加了竞争
the auction and even though that players
拍卖，即使那个球员
know exactly where that reserve is it's
确切知道那是哪里的储备金
it's raising the overall revenue in the
它正在提高整体收入
second price auction so this is
第二次价格拍卖，所以这是
something that that has been looked at
已经看过的东西
more generally and so in terms of the
更一般地说，
overall design of optimal auctions what
最佳拍卖的总体设计是什么
do they look like well there's a concept
他们看起来很好吗，有一个概念
which is important in defining these and
在定义这些方面很重要，并且
it's what's known as a bidders virtual
这就是所谓的虚拟投标人
valuation and if you have a true value
估值，如果您具有真实价值
of VI of your virtual valuation is VI
您的虚拟估值中的VI为VI
adjusted subtracting off a you think of
调整后减去您想到的
sort of shading down your value what is
有点掩盖您的价值是什么
it shaded down by what's shaded down by
它被什么阴影了
something which depends
取决于
how how many values were above what you
在您之上有多少个值
what's the probability of having values
有值的概率是多少
above the value that you're expressing
高于您要表达的价值
and then adjusted on the denominator by
然后在分母上调整
the the relative frequency with which
相对频率
you have the valuation that you're
您拥有自己的估值
looking at now exactly understanding the
看现在完全了解
virtual valuation is a fairly difficult
虚拟估值是相当困难的
task it's a fairly deep concept and it
任务是一个很深的概念
has to do with keeping track of exactly
与跟踪准确有关
what the incentive constraints for
激励约束是什么
different values are and and how rapidly
不同的价值，以及发展的速度
you're losing or gaining value as you're
你正在失去或获得价值
moving values up so in terms of how many
提升价值的多少
what's the relative probability of
的相对概率是多少
different types at or above a given
给定或以上的不同类型
level what we're gonna do is assume that
假设我们要做的是
this thing is increasing in VI okay if
这个东西在VI中增加了，如果
it's not increasing in VI then the
VI并没有增加，然后
statements of the theorems we're going
我们要定理的陈述
to make it are going to be more
使它变得更多
complicated so this object will assume
复杂，因此此对象将假定
to be increasing in VI if you check out
如果您签出，将增加VI
this virtual valuation in the case of a
如果是
uniform distribution it turns out to be
均匀分布证明是
2 VI minus 1 so indeed increasing in VI
2 VI减1因此VI的确增加
and the way in which will set reserve
以及设定储备金的方式
prices is to pick the reserve price to
价格是选择底价
be the level of VI at which the virtual
是虚拟的VI级别
valuation would be exactly equal to zero
估值将完全等于零
okay so if you find the value of VI at
好吧，如果您发现VI的值是
which this is exactly equal to zero
这正好等于零
we'll set we'll call that the bitter
我们将其称为苦味
specific reserve price and in particular
具体底价，尤其是
if you plug back in the uniform
如果你插上制服
distribution for this now you're getting
现在的分布
to VI minus 1 the value of which that
至VI减去1，其中
happens is happens to be 1/2 right so
恰好是1/2对，所以
you would set the reserve price
你会设定底价
individual reserve price at 1/2 okay so
个人底价为1/2还可以
Roger Myerson proved theorem which
罗杰·迈尔森（Roger Myerson）证明了定理
characterized optimal auctions in 1981
1981年进行了最佳拍卖
actually that was part of the work that
实际上那是工作的一部分
earned him the Nobel Prize
为他赢得了诺贝尔奖
along with revelation principle and some
以及启示原理和一些
of the other things we've seen this is a
我们已经看到的其他事情是
has been a fairly influential theorem
一直是一个很有影响力的定理
and so let's have a look at what it says
因此，让我们看看它说了什么
it's a it's a a bit of a mouthful but if
这是一个有点嘴，但如果
we look at the optimal single good
我们来看最优的单品
auction in terms of a direct mechanism
拍卖的直接机制
what's the structure the structure is
结构是什么结构
you're going to sell the good to the
你将把商品卖给
person who has the highest virtual
虚拟度最高的人
valuation based on what they announced
根据他们宣布的估值
okay so look at the different
好吧，所以看看不同的
individuals and instead of looking at
个人，而不是看着
who has the actual highest direct bid
实际最高直接出价的人
we're going to use their virtual
我们将使用他们的虚拟
valuations instead of the direct
估值，而不是直接估值
valuations okay so we're gonna make
估值还可以，所以我们要
adjustments based on these virtual
根据这些虚拟调整
valuations and we'll sell it to that
估值，我们将其出售给
person as long as their value is bigger
人，只要他们的价值更大
than their reserve price if not then we
比他们的底价高
won't sell it to anybody if not if this
如果没有的话，不会卖给任何人
isn't satisfying if the good is sold
如果商品被出售，我不满意
then the winning person is going to be
那么获胜者将是
charged the smallest valuation that that
收取的最低估值
person could have declared and still
一个人可能已经宣布并且仍然
been winner so we look at the smallest
是赢家，所以我们看最小的
valuation that has them still being
估值仍然存在
above their reserve price and still
高于底价，仍然
being the winner and think of that as
成为赢家，并认为这是
sort of the the benchmark of the
有点像基准
equivalent of either the second highest
相当于第二高的
price or the reserve price that's going
价格或要走的底价
to be the value that they have to pay
成为他们必须付出的价值
okay so we have an auction where now
好吧，现在我们有一个拍卖行
what we do is we people put in values
我们要做的就是我们将价值观放在人身上
declare their values for the good but
宣扬其价值，但
now we adjust them via these virtual
现在我们通过这些虚拟的
evaluations and have reserve prices and
评估并具有底价和
choose the person who has the highest
选择最高的人
virtual valuation subject to that being
虚拟估值受制于
above the reserve price and charge them
高于底价并收取费用
the price that they could have gotten in
他们本来可以得到的价格
terms of the lowest valuation they could
他们可以接受的最低估值条款
have announced and still been the winner
已经宣布并仍然是赢家
of this auction okay a corollary of this
这次拍卖的结果是这样的
where you can begin to simplify all of
在这里您可以简化所有
this if we're looking at a symmetric
如果我们正在看一个对称的
setting where everybody has exactly the
设定每个人都有的地方
same distributions like we did earlier
像我们之前所做的一样的分布
in the two bitter case in the second
在第二种痛苦的情况下
price auction case what do we end up
价格拍卖案我们最终会发生什么
with it indeed it turns out that the
事实证明，
optimal auction is a second price
最佳拍卖是第二价格
auction with the reserve price of our
以我们的底价拍卖
star where that reserve price satisfies
底价满足的明星
this equation and in the case of a
这个方程式，如果是
uniform distribution the reserve price
统一分配底价
is going to be 1/2 so it would actually
将是1/2，所以实际上
say that the optimal second auction in
说在
the case of a symmetric setting would be
对称设置的情况是
set your if uniform 0 1 set your reserve
设置您是否统一0 1设置您的储备金
price to 1/2 and then have a situation
价格降到1/2然后有情况
where you do a second price auction
在哪里进行第二次价格拍卖
above that ok so the nice thing about
好的，那么关于
this is it says in symmetric settings
这是说对称设置
things simplify dramatically and you're
事情大大简化，你
running basically second price auctions
基本上进行第二次价格拍卖
with reserve prices and the reserve
底价和底价
price is going to depend on this
价格将取决于此
distribution what's really going on now
分发现在到底发生了什么
you can understand a little more about
您可以了解更多有关
what this virtual valuation is doing in
这种虚拟估值在做什么
terms of adjusting things it's adjusting
调整事物的条件
things too to capture relatively how
东西也无法捕捉
much of the distribution is is is that
大部分的分布是
high values compared to lower values and
高值与低值相比
the reserve price is being pushed up to
底价被推高到
a point where you want to push it so
您想要推动它的地方
that you're making sure that you're not
确保您没有
going so high that you're losing the
太高了，你就失去了
bids of that you're going above the bids
您的出价高于出价
and not going to sell the item but you
并不会出售该物品，但你
want to move it up high enough to have
想要将其向上移动到足以
some competition and that trade-off is
一些竞争，而这种权衡是
is being captured by exactly this
正是被这个捕获了
expression okay so the optimal auction
表达好，所以是最佳拍卖
has some features that we would have
有一些我们会拥有的功能
seen as in a victory Clark growth
被视为克拉克的胜利
mechanism and what's a little bit
机制和一点点
different here is that we have two
不同的是我们有两个
things going on one is that the actual
一件事是，实际
valuations are being adjusted by these
这些正在调整估值
virtual evaluation functions and also
虚拟评估功能以及
it's not looking like a victory Clark
看起来不像是胜利克拉克
goals mechanism in the sense that the
在某种意义上说，目标机制
outcome isn't always efficient sometimes
结果有时并不总是有效的
we do not sell the good in these kinds
我们不出售这类商品
of auctions and you know how should
拍卖，你知道应该如何
bidders really bid in this so the good
竞标者真的在竞标，所以很好
news is that we still have a second
消息是我们还有第二个
price auction kind of format held in
价格拍卖的格式
this virtual evaluation space so the the
这个虚拟评估空间
transformations mean that that it looks
转换意味着它看起来
slightly different in terms of what the
在什么方面略有不同
payments are going to be and when
付款将在何时
somebody ends up winning something
有人最终赢得了一些东西
but the proof that second price auction
但是第二次拍卖的证据
is dominant strategy instead of
是主导策略，而不是
compatible or truthful still works out
兼容或真实仍然可行
here so you still get these nice
在这里，所以你仍然得到这些好
properties in terms of the incentives of
财产的激励
the auction but it's different in terms
拍卖，但在条款上有所不同
of what the specifics are in terms of
具体是什么
the payment rule and we're not always
付款规则，我们并不总是
doing efficient things in this world so
在这个世界上做有效率的事情
here again we see that trade-off that
在这里，我们再次看到
we've seen before in the Myers and
我们之前在Myers和
Satterthwaite theorem here when we're
我们在这里的Satterthwaite定理
trying in this case to get incentive
在这种情况下试图获得激励
compatibility and maximize things for
兼容性和最大化的东西
the seller so the sellers trying to
卖方，所以卖方试图
figure out how they can get the most out
弄清楚他们如何充分利用
of this auction we end up with some
在这次拍卖中，我们最终得到了一些
inefficient trade so the sellers going
交易效率低下，所以卖方去
to actually have to commit to doing this
实际上必须致力于这样做
right so you have to commit to abiding
对，所以您必须承诺遵守
by the reserve price and if everybody's
根据底价，如果每个人都
bid comes in afterwards not saying oh
出价后来才说不出来哦
well sorry I didn't really mean that I'm
很抱歉，我不是真的不是说我
going to revise my reserve price and
要修改我的底价，
drop it down so this mechanism works if
放下它，这样，如果
the the seller can commit to not selling
卖方可以承诺不出售
the object if the bids end up below the
如果出价最终低于
reserve price okay why does this work
保留价格好为什么这样做
what's going on here
这里发生了什么
well reserve prices again are like
好储备价格再次像
competitors they increase the payments
竞争对手，他们增加付款
of the winning bidders the virtual
中标者的虚拟
evaluations why are they playing a role
评价他们为什么发挥作用
here in terms of deciding who's a winner
在决定谁是赢家方面
well if you have strong asymmetries in
如果您在
this auction if you didn't do anything
如果您什么也没做，本次拍卖
and you were the seller it could be that
而你是卖方，可能是
they're really weak bidder basically
他们基本上是弱者
isn't really competing with the strong
并没有真正与强者竞争
bidder
投标人
so by and changing things relative to
因此，通过改变相对于
these virtual evaluations that can make
这些虚拟的评估可以使
weak bidders be more competitive with
弱小的投标人更具竞争力
with strong bidders now that has a plus
现在有强力竞标者
and a minus to it one is that sometimes
缺点是有时
you end up selling it for a lower price
你最终以较低的价格出售
than you would otherwise to the lower
比你要低的多
bidder but other times it actually
投标人，但实际上有时
inflates it means that the the higher
膨胀意味着越高
bidder has to end up paying a higher
投标人不得不最终支付更高的价格
price and it effectively increases the
价格，有效地增加了
competition there and in some sense
在某种意义上说那里的竞争
makes the bidding more aggressive okay
使出价更具侵略性
so that's been a quick look at optimal
因此快速了解了最佳
auctions the proofs of
拍卖的证据
these results are actually quite
这些结果实际上是相当
involved and involves some calculus of
涉及并涉及到一些演算
variations and some delicate arguments
变化和一些微妙的论点
they are worth looking into if you
他们值得研究，如果你
really enjoy this stuff dig into
非常喜欢这东西挖
meyerson's paper and a whole series of
迈耶森的论文以及一系列
ones that have followed up on that there
在那里跟进的
they're interesting papers and the
他们是有趣的论文，
techniques behind them have become used
他们背后的技术已被使用
in other kinds of mechanism design
在其他类型的机制设计中
arguments more generally but what we
争论更普遍，但是我们
want to take away from this is is a
想要摆脱的是一个
couple of things one is that there are
几件事之一是，有
that the problems are well-defined and
问题是明确定义的，
they're well-defined solutions to
他们是明确定义的解决方案
solving four mechanisms that satisfy
解决四个满足的机制
certain properties the ones we've been
某些属性，我们去过的
more interested in and probably are more
更感兴趣，也许更多
interested in from a societal point of
从社会的角度对
view is how do we maximize overall
观点是我们如何整体上最大化
efficiency total utilities but sometimes
总效用，但有时
we're also interested in understanding
我们也有兴趣了解
how sellers might act in a market or you
卖方如何在市场或您中行事
know they might want to maximize revenue
知道他们可能想最大化收益
not do the efficient thing how are they
没有做有效率的事情，他们怎么样
going to act what kinds of mechanisms
要采取什么样的机制
are they going to choose and so
他们会选择，所以
mechanism design you can put down
可以放下的机制设计
whatever objective you want in terms of
您想要的任何目标
what you're trying to maximize is it
您想要最大化的是
overall societal welfare is it revenue
整体社会福利是收入吗
it could be some combination and in
可能是一些组合
those kinds of situations once you're
那种情况一旦你
going to do that then you put in
然后去做
incentive compatibility constraints
激励相容性约束
that's actually part of what goes into
这实际上是其中一部分
the proof of meyerson's theorem put
迈耶森定理的证明
those things in and maximize subject to
那些东西并最大化地受
those constraints and see what falls out
这些约束条件，看看会发生什么
and that can give you a very general
那可以给你非常笼统的
recipe for for optimal mechanism design
优化机械设计的配方